Subindex build by Linnet
http://linnet.126.com  http://blog.csdn.net/redbirdli
火鸟字幕合并器SubindexV0.5
Created time 09.09.08 00:05:57
听着,先生,我最后一次告诉你 我不在乎电脑上登记了什么
Listen, sir, for the Iast time, I don't care what the computer says.
我们没有从房间冰箱 拿走一包糖果
We did not take a bag of Mashuga Nuts from the minibar.
我们没有看《热心助人的医生》
And we did not watch Dr. Do-Me-A-Little.
-乔伊,昨晚你到过我们房间? -没有
-Joey, were you in our room Iast night? -No.
他们说电影片名 不会出现在帐单上
I was toId the name of the movie wouId not appear on the biII.
-我们要退掉新房了 -没错,我不再是新娘
-We're checking out of the bridaI suite. -That's right, I'm no Ionger a bride.
我永远都当不了新娘 现在我是某人的太太
I'II never be a bride again. Now I'm just someone's wife.
现在我是全世界最快乐的男人
And I'm the happiest guy in the worId.
甜心,别难过 我们还是有很光明的未来
Honey, don't be upset. We stiII have so much to Iook forward to.
对
Yeah, right.
-我们还要去度蜜月 -那是星期四的事
-We got the honeymoon. -That's not tiII Thursday.
-还有婚纱照 -那得等上好几个星期
-The wedding pictures. -It won't be ready for weeks.
但婚宴上用即可拍 拍的照片马上可以洗好
Not the disposabIe cameras from the tabIes.
没错 我就知道我嫁给你是有原因的
That's true. I knew I married you for a reason!
听着,我拿照片去洗 你先回家吧
TeII you what, I wiII go get them deveIoped, and you can go home.
-什么?你拍了什么? -没什么
-What? What did you take a picture of? -Nothing.
一定很精彩
It was something.
即可拍在罗斯那里 他还没有退房吗?
Ross has the cameras. Has he checked out yet?
你在开玩笑吗? 退房时间是中午
Are you joking? Checkout is not tiII noon.
-他还有11分钟 -所以呢?
-And he has a good 1 1 minutes Ieft. -So?
罗斯从来不会 提早退房
So Ross had never checked out of a room a minute before he had to.
我们在交往的时候 有一次延后退房
One time, when we were dating, we got a Iate checkout.
他非常兴奋 那是我们最棒的性经验
He got so excited, it was the best sex we ever had.
直到他最后 大叫着“拉迪森”
UntiI he screamed out ''Radisson'' at the end.
好吧,我去找罗斯拿照相机 然后把底片拿去洗
Okay, weII, I'm gonna get Ross, get the cameras and get them deveIoped.
乔伊,你32岁了
32, Joe. You're 32!
-这是你的帐单 -谢谢
-Here's a copy of your biII. -Thanks.
香槟,草莓…
Champagne, strawberries....
天啊,我不敢相信 钱德在我们的新婚之夜看黄色电影
Oh, my God! I can't beIieve ChandIer ordered porn on our wedding night.
对,那真的很惨 糖果?
Yeah, that's sad. Mashuga Nut?
片名:六人行 红色毛衣
欢迎光临 淘宝店--迷失蔚蓝 lost in blue (PSP影视\游戏) http://shop34826882.taobao.com/
主演:珍妮佛安妮斯顿
主演:寇妮考克斯
主演:丽莎库卓
主演:麦特勒布兰
主演:马修派瑞
主演:大卫修蒙
我还有六分钟
I have six minutes Ieft!
是我
It's me.
肥皂,洗发精 你真的要这些东西带走?
Soaps, shampoos. Are you reaIIy taking aII this stuff?
为什么不行? 这全包含在房费里
Why not? It's buiIt into the price of the room.
对,但你不需要… 这是什么?
Yeah, but you don't need-- What is this?
针线包
Thread.
答对了
Score!
-即可拍在哪里? -什么即可拍?
-Where are the disposabIe cameras? -What cameras?
-昨晚我把它们交给你 -才没有
-Last night I asked you to take them. -No, you didn't.
就是有,记得吗? 在切蛋糕前我说…
Yes, remember? Right before we cut the cake, I said--
对,你问我 能不能帮你一个忙
Yeah, you asked me if I couId do you a favor.
这时墨瑞叔叔走过来 交给你一张支票
Then my UncIe Murray came up to you and handed you a check.
制片:温蒂诺勒
Then you said, ''Why is it caIIed a check? Why not a YugosIavian?''
然后你说“它为什么叫做支票? 为什么不叫南斯拉夫人?”
编剧:戴娜克莱恩布考
然后你那么做 墨瑞叔叔这样看着我
Then you did that, and my UncIe Murray Iooked at me Iike:
-即可拍不在你手上? -没错,抱歉
-So you don't have the cameras? -No, sorry.
什么?相机不见了? 摩妮卡会气疯的
So, what? They're gone? Monica's gonna freak!
我相信它们应该就在某个地方 我帮你找
I'm sure they're here somewhere. I'II heIp you Iook.
导演:大卫修蒙
-Great. -In three minutes.
-太棒了 -再等三分钟
你要丢下钱德 自己拆礼物?
Are you gonna open the presents without ChandIer?
不,我只是…
No! I'm just....
它们在呼换我 这个小家伙甚至爬到我的膝盖上
They're caIIing out to me. This IittIe guy even crawIed up in my Iap.
钱德不会介意我拆开一样礼物 你觉得它是什么?
ChandIer wouIdn't mind if I opened just one present. What do you think it is?
是一面小镜子 只要你一照它…
A IittIe mirror that, when you Iook into it...
你会发现自己变成了老太婆
...you see yourseIf as an oId woman.
是一个迷你盐罐
A tiny saIt shaker!
天啊,是用来装迷你盐的
Oh, my God, for tiny saIt!
好吧,那真的很好玩 很好玩
Oh, wow! Okay. WeII, that was fun. That was fun.
我会等钱德 一起拆开其他礼物
Okay, I'II just wait for ChandIer to open up the rest of them.
但这只是调味瓶组的 一部份
AIthough, you know, this is part of a saIt-and-pepper set.
或许它只算半项礼物 你觉得呢?
It may just count as onIy haIf a present. What do you think?
我猜如果它是一套的,再拆开一样 应该没关系,或许是这个
I guess it's okay to open one more if it's part of a set. It's probabIy this one.
或是这个
Or this one!
-你好吗?会害喜吗? -男生们还不知道吧?
-How are you? Got any morning sickness? -The guys don't know yet, do they?
乔伊跟罗斯什么都不知道 钱德认为是菲比怀孕了
Joey and Ross don't know anything. ChandIer thinks Phoebe's pregnant.
没错 钱德还是以为我怀孕了
That's right. ChandIer does stiII think I'm pregnant.
他没有问我感觉如何 也没有帮我提袋子
He hasn't asked me how I'm feeIing or offered to carry my bags.
我为跟他在一起的女人 觉得难过
I feeI bad for the woman who ends up with him.
我是指在你之后的女人
After you, of course.
别担心,你只需要 再假装怀孕几小时…
Don't worry. You onIy have to be pregnant for a few more hours...
因为今天我要告诉孩子的爸
...because I'm teIIing the father today.
他就住在这栋公寓吗? 是一楼那个高个貌吗?
Is it someone in the buiIding? That taII guy on the first fIoor?
-不 -什么?我觉得他很可爱
-No! -What? I think he's cute.
-那么你可以去怀他的孩子 -相信我,我正在努力
-Then you have his baby. -BeIieve me, I'm trying.
这真的好奇怪 你今天要告诉这个男人…
It's so weird. You're gonna teII this guy today...
他不知道 会发生什么事
...and he has no idea what's gonna happen.
你要敲敲他的门 永远地改变他的一生
You're just gonna knock on his door and change his Iife forever.
你就像艾德麦马汉 只不过手上没有拿大额支票
You're Iike Ed McMahon, except without the big check.
也没有原始的性吸引力
Or the raw sexuaI magnetism.
对,我猜 那是个大消息
Yeah, weII, I guess it is pretty big news.
大消息?它是超级大消息 天啊,这个男人什么都不知道
Pretty big? It's huge! God, this guy doesn't have a cIue.
他走在街上心想 “我跟瑞秋葛林做爱,太帅了”
He's just waIking down the street thinking, ''I had sex with RacheI Greene. I rock!''
然后,碰,他当了爸爸 一切都不一样了
Then, bam! He's a father, everything's different.
除非他真的想当爸爸 我不会对他提出任何要求
It's onIy different if he wants it to be. I'm not gonna ask him for anything.
他还是得做出 重大的决定
He stiII has this huge decision to make.
现在他边走边想 “我要当爸爸吗?”然后,碰
Now he's waIking around thinking, ''Do I want to be a dad?'' Then, bam!
这次怎么了?
What was that ''bam''?
我不知道 他可能是撞上巴士了
I don't know. He's hit by a bus, or something.
乔伊,如果跟你上过床的女人 告诉你她怀孕了,你会怎么办?
Joey, what wouId you do if someone you sIept with toId you she was pregnant?
谁打电话到这里来?
Who caIIed here?
她听起来像金发美女吗?她有口音吗? 我得去打个电话
Did she sound bIond? Did she have an accent? I gotta make a caII.
我不该到 那家太阳眼镜专卖店的
ShouId have never waIked into that SungIass Hut!
不是你 你没有让任何人怀孕
It's not you! You didn't get anybody pregnant.
你为什么要那样子吓我? 发生了什么事?
Why wouId you scare me Iike that? What the heII's going on?
有人怀孕了吗?
Is somebody pregnant?
对,我怀孕了
Oh, yeah! That's me.
天啊,菲比 你要生孩子了?
Oh, my God, Pheebs! You're gonna have a baby?
对 天啊,我要生孩子了
Yes, I am. Oh, my God, I'm gonna have a baby!
-等一下,孩子的爸是谁? -你不认识他
-Wait a minute, who's the father? -You don't know him.
那不重要 他不希望跟我或孩子扯上关系
It's not important. He wants nothing to do with me or the baby.
这家伙是谁? 因为我要把他找出来,痛扁他一顿
Who is this guy? Because I wiII track him down and kick his ass!
-大卫林恩 -大卫林恩
-David Linn. -David Linn!
-谁是大卫林恩? -我在健身房认识的人,他很讨厌
-Who's David Linn? -Some guy from my gym. LittIe annoying.
-钱德 -你找到即可拍了吗?
-ChandIer? -Did you find the cameras?
-没有,你呢? -我找到了
-No. Did you? -Yes.
那就是我躲在桌下的原因 我想要庆祝
That's why I'm under the tabIe, ceIebrating.
我去失物中心问过管理员 没有人捡到即可拍
I checked in the Iost and found. I taIked to the manager. No one's turned them in.
太棒了,今天只有那些即可拍 能让摩妮卡打起精神来
Great. Those cameras were the onIy thing that was gonna cheer Monica up today.
你们刚刚结婚 她为什么要心情不好?
You just got married. Why is she so depressed?
我没有力气 问她那个问题
AII my energy is going into not asking that question.
-我不敢相信我搞砸了 -我很遗憾,兄弟
-I can't beIieve I screwed this up! -I'm sorry, man.
我有个点子 你们在这个宴会厅请客
Here's a thought. This is the same baIIroom.
这里有乐队 等一下会有很多人盛装前来
There's a band. There's gonna be pIenty of dressed-up peopIe.
你建议 我们可以丢下问题不管?
Are you suggesting we dance our troubIes away?
不,我是说我们到礼品店 买一些即可拍…
No, I'm saying we buy more of these at the gift shop...
换上礼服 拍几张照片
...throw our tuxes back on and take a few pictures.
我们只要 不拍到任何人的脸
We just have to make sure not to get anybody's faces.
你是认真的吗?
Are you serious?
我想到 在家等你的新娘
I'm thinking about your new bride at home.
你想在你们共度一生的第一天 就让她失望吗?
Do you want to start your Iife together by Ietting her down?
你真的要给我关于婚姻的建议?
Marriage advice? ReaIIy?
我是在告诉你 这看起来很像你的婚宴
I'm teIIing you, this Iooks exactIy Iike your wedding.
-这些花都一样吧? -我不知道,花是摩妮卡挑的
-Aren't these the same fIowers? -I don't know. Monica picked them.
-椅子呢? -也是
-What about the chairs? -Those too.
-布置呢? -她挑的
-The pIace settings? -Her.
-你做了什么? -我负责看好照相机
-What did you do? -I was in charge of the cameras.
礼品店?
Gift shop?
-你说了吗? -还没有
-Did you do it yet? -Not yet.
那么你在这里做什么? 你真的要说吗?
Then what are you doing here? Are you about to do it?
是阿甘吗?
Is it Gunther?
-不是阿甘 -谢天谢地,还好宝宝不会有他的头发
-It's not Gunther! -Thank God. Because that hair on a baby?
孩子的爸不在这里,好吗? 我还没有告诉他
The father is not here, okay? I haven't toId him yet.
-我想现在我没办法告诉他 -为什么?
-I don't think I can teII him at aII now. -Why not?
我在街上边走边想 “我要告诉孩子的爸”,然后,碰
I was waIking down the street, thinking, ''I'm gonna teII the father.'' And then, bam!
你撞到了巴士?
Bus?
不,是你,你吓了我一跳 你一直在提醒我这是件大事
No, you! You freaked me out. You kept saying how huge this aII is.
但它的确是件大事
But it is huge.
我知道,我只是在想 它对我来说有多重要
I know. But I was just thinking about how huge it was for me.
我根本不知道 这对孩子的爸来说有多重要
I didn't even go to how huge it'II be for the father.
你想太多了 告诉他,把事情做个了断
You're thinking about this way too much. Just teII him and get it over with.
它就像撕掉OK绷一样 越快越不痛,你看
It's Iike ripping off this Band-Aid, quick and painIess. Watch.
天杀的…
Oh, mother of--!
看吧?
See?
-我们要拆礼物了吗? -不,我根本不该拆开礼物
-Are we opening presents? -No. I shouIdn't have even opened these.
乔伊,我控制不了自己 你得帮我一个忙
Joey, I am out of controI! You have to do me a favor.
不论我说什么 不论我做什么…
No matter what I say, no matter what I do...
拜,不要让我 再拆开任何礼物,好吗?
...pIease, do not Iet me open another present. Okay?
再给我一个礼物
Give me one more.
很好,你来了 菲比,听我说…
Oh, good, you're here. Pheebs? Listen....
-坐下,我要告诉你一件事 -好吧
-Sit down, I got something I wanna say. -AII right.
外面的世界很可怕 特别是对单亲妈妈来说
It's a scary worId out there, especiaIIy for a singIe mom.
我一直觉得 我跟你之间很特别
I've aIways feIt that you and I have a speciaI bond.
所以…
So....
菲比布非,你愿意嫁给我吗?
Phoebe Buffay, wiII you marry me?
我的天啊
Oh, my God!
我愿意嫁给你
Oh, yeah, I'II marry you.
-你不能嫁给他 -小姐,你结过婚了,这次轮到我
-You can't marry him! -Hey, Iady, your day's over. It's my turn.
-她为什么不能嫁给我? -我可以,我也愿意
-Why can't she marry me? -I can and I wiII.
她没有怀孕 是瑞秋怀孕了
She's not pregnant. RacheI's the one who's pregnant.
天啊
Oh, my God!
九个月后你生不出孩子 他会发现的
He'd notice when you didn't have a baby in nine months!
他是乔伊
It's Joey!
我爱你
I love you.
等一下,我不敢相信 瑞秋怀孕了?孩子的爸是谁?
Wait, I can't beIieve it! RacheI's pregnant? Who's the father?
我们不知道
We don't know.
-不知道是不是那个家伙 -哪个家伙?
-I wonder if it's that dude. -There's a dude?
是谁呢?
Who is it?
大约一个月前 这家伙跟瑞秋共度春宵
About a month ago this guy spent the night with RacheI.
我没有看到他,但是…
I didn't see who it was, but....
他把故事说完了吗?
Was that story over?
那个家伙留下这个
The guy Ieft this.
天啊 我知道孩子的爸是谁
Oh, my God! I know who the father is.
说故事的人 得把故事说完
PeopIe have got to finish their stories.
哈
HeIIo.
我不知道我们有没有都照进去 靠近一点
I don't know if we're both in. Come cIoser.
你的古龙水味道很好闻
Nice aftershave.
如果你想来一点 我包包里有八罐随身瓶
If you want some, I've got eight mini bottIes in my bag.
-对不起,你能帮我们拍照吗? -没问题
-Excuse me, couId you take a picture of us? -Of course.
你能帮我们照一张吗?
WouId you take one of us?
没问题
Yeah, sure.
喀
CIick.
-我没有听到快门声 -我听到了
-It didn't cIick. -I heard it.
-但闪光灯没亮 -你为什么不帮我们拍照?
-But there was no fIash. -Why won't you take our picture?
对,我会帮你们拍照
Oh, yeah. I'II take your picture.
你的手指挡到镜头了
Your finger was covering the Iens.
你是安瑟亚当斯吗? 快滚吧
Who are you, AnseI Adams? Get out of here!
(中央咖啡厅)
听着,我真的很难过 之前我吓坏你了…
Look, I feeI reaIIy bad about how I freaked you out before...
所以我请孩子的爸到里面等你 你可以告诉他事实
...so I asked the father to meet you here so you couId teII him.
什么?等一下 你怎么知道孩子的爸是谁?
What? Wait a minute. How do you even know who the father is?
或许有时候我傻傻的…
I may pIay the fooI at times...
但事实上我是个勇不放弃的 金发美女
...but I'm more than a pretty bIond girI with an ass that won't quit.
我相信 这是孩子爸的衣服…
I beIieve this beIongs to the father of your baby...
天啊,他就在里面?
Oh, God. He's in there right now?
你可以转身离开或是长痛不如短痛 你打算怎么做?
You can turn around, or you can go rip the Band-Aid off. What do you want to do?
-我们把事情做个了断吧 -你确定?
-Let's rip. -Are you sure?
-菲比 -好吧,抱歉
-Phoebe! -Okay. Sorry.
瑞秋
Hey, Rach.
你为什么不到台上呢? 我要拍张你说话时的照片
Why don't you go up on-stage. I'II get a picture of you doing the speech.
1995年别克李萨布利的车主 请跟柜联络
WiII the owner of a 1 995 Buick LeSabre pIease see the front desk?
你的车就要被拖走了
Your car is about to be towed.
那是我的车
That's my car!
-1995年的李萨布利? -对
-A '95 LeSabre? -Yes.
-绿色的李萨布利? -对
-A green LeSabre? -Yes!
-抱歉,我是说蓝色的李萨布利 -对,我的车是蓝绿色的
-I'm sorry, I meant a bIue LeSabre. -Yes, green-bIue.
快去把它移开吧
WeII, go. Go move it!
准备要拍最后一张照片了吗? 拍完马上就跑
Ready for the Iast picture? Get ready to run.
恭喜
CongratuIations on your wedding.
这是怎么一回事?
So, what's this about?
瑞秋有事 要告诉你
RacheI has something she wants to teII you.
我相信 这是你的红毛衣
And I beIieve that this is your red sweater.
不,这才是我的红毛衣
No, this is my red sweater.
不
Oh, no.
有人要喝咖啡吗?
CouId I get anyone a coffee?
或是毒药?没有吗?只有我要?好吧
Or poison? No? Just for me? Okay.
发生了什么事?瑞秋
What's going on, Rach?
没事 菲比弄错了
Nothing. Phoebe kind of made a mistake.
但你的确常穿那件毛衣 你在做什么冒险的事吗?
But you do wear that sweater a Iot. Are you invoIved in some kind of dare?
事实上我很高兴能接到菲比的电话
I'm actuaIIy gIad Phoebe caIIed.
我知道我们会分手是因为你觉得 我太幼稚,但我已经长大了
I know we broke up because you thought I was immature, but I've grown up.
我想我们应该复合
I think we shouId get back together.
时机不对
It's just not the right time.
时机非常恰当 我做了万全的准备
It is the right time. I'm ready for more.
来吧,瑞秋 我们可以再试一次
Come on, Rach. Let's give it another try.
我怀孕了
I'm having a baby.
-你可以走了 -谢谢
-You can go. -Thank you.
我不知道 礼物怎么会是打开的
I don't know how any of these got opened!
-你拆开了所有的礼物? -我知道,我是个可怕的人
-You opened them aII? -I know, I am a terribIe person.
钱德永远都不会 再相信我任何事
ChandIer's never gonna trust me with anything ever again.
你拆开了我爸妈的礼物
You got my parents' gift.
-那是什么? -应该是跟义大利腊肠有关的东西
-What is that? -I think it does something to saIami.
-情况如何? -泰格怎么说?
-How'd it go? -What did Tag say?
泰格不是孩子的爸 乔伊知道了?
Tag is not the father. And Joey knows now?
我知道了,瑞秋 我为你感到高兴
I do, Rach, I do. And I am so happy for you.
你没有试着 要解开我的胸罩
Wow, you didn't even try to unhook my bra.
-你要告诉孩子的爸吗? -我会的,只是今晚我不想那么做
-So are you ever gonna teII whoever it is? -I wiII. I'm just not up for it tonight.
不论这家伙说什么 你不会独自面对这一切
No matter what this guy says, you're not gonna be aIone in this.
-是吗? -不,听着…
-I'm not? -No. Listen....
外面的世界很可怕 特别是对单亲妈妈来说
It's a scary worId out there, especiaIIy for a singIe mom.
我一直觉得 我跟你之间很特别
I've aIways feIt Iike you and I have this speciaI bond, you know?
-瑞秋葛林,你愿意嫁给我吗? -什么?
-RacheI Greene, wiII you marry me? -What?
-什么? -什么?
-What? -What?!
-菲比,把戒指还给我 -不
-Pheebs, give me the ring back. -No!
乔伊,你真的很体贴 但我不要一个丈夫
Joey, you're so sweet, so sweet, honey. But I'm not Iooking for a husband.
我了解
I understand.
对不起 我想去躺一下
WeII, if you'II excuse me, I'm going to go and Iie down.
乔伊
什么?我跟你求过婚 这样才公平
What? I proposed to you. It baIances out.
我不能说我不心痛
I can't say that didn't hurt.
但我会原谅你,乔伊崔比亚尼
But I'II take you back, Joey Tribbiani.
-听着,我只是说… -义大利腊肠用具
-Listen, about that, I onIy offered-- -Ooh, a SaIami Buddy!
来吧
There you go!
-我们回来了 -太棒了
-We're back! -Great.
我们待在厨房吧 待在厨房就好了
We're hanging in the kitchen. Let's stay in the kitchen.
-现在是看照片时间 -你一定会喜欢的
-It's picture time. -You're gonna Iove these.
这是罗斯的照片
Here's a picture of Ross.
那是我
And that's me.
我跟罗斯
And that's me and Ross.
这是我们第一次 以新婚夫妻身份接吻的照片
And here's a picture of our first kiss as a married coupIe.
那张照片真的很棒
Wow, that is a great picture. Yeah!
真的太有趣了 因为我在我们的行李里找到即可拍
And interesting, because I found the cameras in one of our bags.
我没想到这一点
Didn't see that coming.
这不是 我们第一次接吻的照片…
So this isn't a picture of our first kiss...
但它的确是 我跟这位女士第一次接吻的照片
...but it is a picture of my first kiss with this Iady.
从你脸上的表情看来 我相信你会记得,所以我不必…
Which, by the Iook on your face, I'm sure you'II remember, so there's no need....
-我会拿真的底片去洗 -好主意
-I'II take the reaI pictures to get deveIoped. -Good idea.
你不管我自己拆开所有礼物? 我们说好要一起拆的
You opened aII the presents without me? We were gonna do that together.
你吻了另一个女人?
You kissed another woman?!
-我们扯平了? -好吧
-CaII it even? -Okay.
-我要把花＝插到花瓶里 -你偷走了那个婚礼的花?
-I'm gonna go get these in some water. -You stoIe those from that wedding?
不,这是饭店大厅的花 他们以为能超收我黄色电影…
No, the hoteI Iobby. They think they can charge me for some dirty movie...
还有一袋糖果的钱 我一定要讨回公道
...and a bag of Mashuga Nuts, they got another thing coming!
我的毛衣
Hey, my sweater!
我找这件毛衣 找了一个月
I've been Iooking for this for, Iike, a month.
我的天啊
Oh, my God!
-你好吗? -我很好,好久不见
-Hey, how you doing? -Good. Long time no see.
-我喜欢你的毛衣 -我也是
-Like your sweater. -Right back at you.
-瑞秋的事真的太疯狂了 -她一直都疯疯癫癫的
-It's crazy about RacheI. -WeII, she's one crazy Iady.
-到底是谁的呢? -我不知道,应该是个义大利人吧
-So whose is it? -I don't know, some ItaIian guy.
少来了,看看你自己的标签 后会有期,他真是奇怪
Come on, read your own IabeI. See you Iater. He is so weird.